<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ጉዞ ኢትዮጵያ</string>
    <!-- Tabs -->

    <string name="place_tab">ቦታ</string>
    <string name="hotel_tab">ሆቴል</string>
    <string name="travelagencies_tab">የጉዞ ኤጀንሲ</string>
    <string name="map_tab">ካርታ</string>

    <!-- appbar options -->
    <string name="setting">Setting</string>
    <string name="share">Share</string>

    <string name="ethiopia_background">ethiopia_background</string>
    <!-- Places -->

    <string name="lalibela">ላሊበላ</string>
    <string name="lalibela_description">This was renamed for King Lalibela (1181-1221) of the Zagwe Dynasty which ruled in Lalibela for more than a century.
        The construction of eleven rock-hewn churches is attributed to King Lalibela.
        The buildings are monolithic, carved from a sloping mass of red volcanic scoria underlaid by dark grey basalt and interconnected by a maze of tunnels and passages with openings to hermit caves and catacombs.
    Some are of the basilica type, having archaic features and imitating architectural elements from earlier periods,
        yet they differ in design and style. Two are decorated with interesting wall paintings and carved figures.
        The Lalibela churches are included in the World Heritage List;
        the principal edifices are the Churches of Medhane Alem, Maryam, Ammanuel, Giyorgis and Golgota-Mikaïl.
    </string>


    <string name="unity_park">የአንድነት ፓርክ</string>
    <string name="unity_park_desc">

        The newly-branded “Unity Park” resides on the 40 hectacres (around 100 acres) of palace grounds set aside on a high,
    green hunk of the cityscape. Emperor Menelik II tagged it for The Grand Palace when Addis Ababa became
    Ethiopia’s new capital in the 19th century.
    This new attraction’s opening last week even generated coverage in the Washington Post and the UK’s Guardian (which took a much broader view of how this connects with Addis’s runaway train development writ large). After visiting Unity Park myself, I want to offer my own earnest recommendation for would-be visitors or curious current Addis residents. It’s worth seeing. Probably more than once. Even though Unity Park’s very much still a work in progress. My kudos come with some serious caveats attached. It nonetheless seems that a sincere effort was made to create a place to tease your brain and find some peace in the chaotic heart of Addis.

    </string>


    <string name="axum_name">አክሱም</string>
    <string name="axum_desc">
        It is a place soaked in legends. Thought to have been the abode of the Queen of Sheba and the ultimate resting
spot of the Ark of the Covenant,this is one of the most ancient towns in total Africa. Find over the fences of the
St Mary of Zion Church Complex where the Ark is probably kept and go to the Northern Stelea Field to find the
old Aksumite Obelisks. In spite of the magnificent history in this place, because it’s a tiny city,Aksum is
frequently overlooked by travelers. Relish locating the remains throughout the town, travel mountaintop
monasteries, and visit below ground to see Aksumite empire graves. Don’t miss Mai Shum, a big rock carved
water body that native tribes think the Queen of Sheba utilized as her bath.
    </string>

    <string name="ertale_name">ኤርታሌ</string>

    <string name="ertale_desc">
One of Africa\'s most striking geographical features is a giant tear across the earth\'s surface visible even
        from space: the Great Rift Valley. Extending from the Middle East to Mozambique,
        the Rift Valley passes in a north-easterly to South-westerly direction right through Ethiopia,
        endowing the country with some spectacular sights range from hot, dry, and barren places to a string of beautiful lakes.
        This tremendous collapse of the earth\'s surface occurred at the same time that the Arabia Peninsula, geologically a part of Africa.
        The Afar Depression is a plate tectonic triple junction where the spreading ridges that are forming the Red Sea and the Gulf of Aden emerge on land and meet the East African Rift.
        The Afar Depression is one of two places on Earth where a mid-ocean ridge can be studied on land, the other being Iceland. At present, the Afar is slowly being pulled apart at a rate of 1-2 cm per year.
        The floor of the Afar Depression is composed mostly of basaltic lava.
        The Afar Depression and Triple Junction also mark the location of a mantle plume, a great uprising of mantle that melts to yield basalt.

    </string>


    <string name="dankil_name">ደንከል</string>
    <string name="dankil_desc">
Located on the frontier between Ethiopia and Eritrea is the Danakil Depression. It’s formally one of the aridest
and warmest spots on Earth. With temperatures that frequently pass 50+ degrees, it’s effortless to find why.
This is a surreal slice of land that’s scattered with active volcanoes, salted basins, warm springs, and a lava lake
– all of which merge to form very moon-like scenery. Lying below sea level, it’s the lowest spot in Africa and
second on earth (after the Dead Sea). Do a little bit of groundwork before you visit as the climate can be severe
if you aren’t ready. But the charm and enigma of this location make any arrangement well worth it.

</string>

    <string name="fasil_named">ጎንደር</string>
    <string name="fasil_desc">
        The 18th century of Ethiopia was Gondar, where then Emperor Fasiladas established his legendary fortresses.
This UNESCO World Heritage Site is today a beautiful museum compound and a wonderful tourist attractions
in Ethiopia that exhibitsthe final centuries of the country’s kings. Sitting in a bowl of hills, the Camelot of
Africa is a wonderful view. The prosperity and magnificence of thisold epicenter can still be found in the
present day town. In spite of its size, Gondar is unusually walkable – begin from the Italian piazza in the town
center and take a walk through tin-covered stone edifices. Wonderful shopping, eateries, and hotels are all
accessible in this place.In adjacent Gorgora you’ll see a little but magnificent Christian monastery
    </string>

    <string name="bluenile_named">ጭስ አባይ</string>
    <string name="bluenile_desc">
        The Nile River is the lengthiest in Africa and its two headwaters are the White Nile and the Blue Nile. The Blue
Nile starts in Ethiopia and along its route you’ll see the Blue Nile Falls – a site to opponent Niagara. Nearly 90
minutes from Bahar Dar the surroundings in this place is really stunning. Locally familiar as Tis Abbay, or ‘
great smoke,’ the falls are nearly 45 meters elevated during the rainy season. Right downstream from the falls
you’ll see Ethiopia’s early stone bridge, established in the 17th century
    </string>


    <string name="nechsar_named">ነጭ ሳር ብሔራዊ ፓርክ</string>
    <string name="nechsar_desc">
        One of the biggest tourist attractions in Ethiopia, this national park is located in southwest of the country. Its
mixed land extends over slopes, wetlands, and jungle. Zebras and gazelles wander the huge grassy land of the
Nechisar Plains. The big, brown-red Lake Abaya lies on the north side of the hilly “Bridge of God” passage. To
the south is Lake Chamo, familiar for its large Nile crocodiles. The park is the abode to plenty of birds,
incorporating the endangered Nechisar nightjar.
    </string>





    <!-- hotels -->
    <string name="skyligt_hotelname">Ethiopian Skylight Hotel</string>
    <string name="skyligt_hoteladrees">Bole Addis Ababa </string>
    <string name="skyligt_hotelPhone">Tel : 011 681 8181</string>

    <string name="golden_hotelname">Golden Tulip Addis Ababa</string>
    <string name="goldenhoteladrees">Bole Addis Ababa </string>
    <string name="golden_hotelPhone">Tel : 011 617 0740</string>


    <string name="hailegondar_hotelname">Haile Resort-Gondar</string>
    <string name="hailegondar_hoteladrees">Gondar </string>
    <string name="hailegondar_hotelPhone">Tel :  +25122 2114 9 95</string>

    <string name="planet_hotelname">Planet Hotel</string>
    <string name="planet_hoteladrees">Hawulti, Mekʼelē, Ethiopia </string>
    <string name="planet_hotelPhone">Tel : 034 440 5660</string>

    <string name="unison_hotelname">
Unison Hotel and Spa </string>
    <string name="unison_hoteladrees">Set in Bahir Dar </string>
    <string name="unison_hotelPhone">Tel : 094 579 7979
</string>


    <string name="hailehawasa_hotelname"> Haile Resort Hawassa</string>
    <string name="hailehawasa_hoteladrees"> Hawassa, Āwasa, Ethiopia  </string>
    <string name="hailehawasa_hotelPhone">Tel : 096 331 3131</string>




    <!-- Travel agencies -->
    <string name="imagin_travellname">Imagine Ethiopia Tours </string>
    <string name="welcom_travellname">welcome Ethiopia tour </string>
    <string name="aman_travellname"> Amran Ethiopia tour and travel</string>
    <string name="base_travellname">Base Ethiopia International Tour
        and Travel PLC </string>
    <string name="yema_travellname"> yema ethiopia tour</string>
    <string name="ethio_travellname"> Ethio target tours</string>
    <string name="fklm_travellname">FKLM Ethiopia Tours, Travel and Car Rental </string>
    <string name="abba_travellname">Abba travel plc head office  </string>




    <string name="hint_entername">please Enter your name</string>
    <string name="hint_enteremail">please Enter your email address</string>
    <string name="registration">If You want to receive emails about  Amazing up coming events, please register below. </string>


</resources>